CHO-YUN, LEI

PERSONAL PROFILE

Bachelor's graduate professional in computer science, with multiple national competition experiences and a research assistant of a professor. Strong communication skills developed from leading a competition team and the ability to work efficiently as a team or individual.

WORK EXPERIENCE

TA of web programming

Chang Gung University | Feb 2023 - June 2023

 Graded assigned homework and held office hours for a class of 65 students

Research Assistant

Chang Gung University | May 2023 - July 2023

- Study the feasibility of language model for medical diagnosis
- · Study the influence of prompt engineering

PROJECTS

Diabetes prediction analysis

 Analyze diabetes datasets from Kaggle and UCI's medical dataset, using ML and DL approach to find the correlations between diabetes and risk factors

Obstacle detection on the railway system

 build a system including railway obstacle detection, real-time streaming, and real-time alarm system

PDF decode cloud service

simulate the real-world experience of cloud services

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

Chang Gung University

BA Computer Science | Nov 2019 - June 2023

- 1st place in capstone project competition
- GPA 3.63/4, IELTS 7.5

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

- C++
- Python
- HTML,CSS,Javescript
- PHP, Mysql

CONTACT ME AT

- 0920250038
- brave.lei40915@gmail.com
- Andrew513.github.com
- Fd., East Dist., Hsinchu City

SKILLS SUMMARY

- Software development
- Image recognition application
- Data engineering
- LLM Prompt engineering
- Database management

AWARDS RECEIVED

- Honorable Mention, Chunghwa Telecom 5G innovation competition (2021)
- Final Round, National
 Intelligent Manufacturing and
 Big Data Analytics
 Contest(2022)
- 1st Place, International ICT Innovative Service Award (2022)